

CHRIS LAWSON CAL POLY UNDERGRAD COMPUTER ENGINEERING



I am a Cal Poly Undergrad and graduate of Atascadero High School. In the Fall of 2020, I will start studing Computer Engineering at Cal Poly SLO. Currently, I am an Network Engineering Intern for a local ISP as well as an alumni programmer from my high school's world-class robotics team.





Years of Experience Java Python Bash/Shell Git/GitHub Electronics CAD GCode



EDUCATION -

Cal Poly SLO, San Luis Obispo, CA

https://cpe.calpolv.edu/

2020 - PRESENT

· Computer Engineering Major

Atascadero High School, Atascadero, CA

http://ahs.atasusd.org/

2016 - 2020

- · High-level, college prep classes
- Peer Mentoring class
- 5 on AP Computer Science Principles test
- · 3 on self-taught AP Computer Science A (Java) test
- Cuesta College Dual-Enrollment Video Production class
- · Cuesta College Dual-Enrollment Calculus class



WORK EXPERIENCE

Wilson Creek Communications - Network Engineering Intern

https://www.wilson-creek.net/

2019 - PRESENT

- Access Point Maintenance
- Customer Technical Support/Installations
- · Backend Server Management

FIRST Robotics Competition - Team 973, Atascadero High School - Programmer

https://www.greybots.com/

2016 - 2020

- C++ Robot Code
- · Custom Web Python/JavaScript Robot Dashboard
- Custom Web JavaScript/Google Sheets/Firebase Time Clock System

LifeGuard CPR and Aquatics, Atascadero - Webmaster

https://lifeguardcpr.com/

2013 - PRESENT

· Implemented WordPress and commerce system for Safety Training Classes



CERTIFICATE & AWARD -

- · 2x Letter in Academics
- Principal's Honor Roll
- The Randy and Sally Knight Youth Scholarship
- 2x AP Scholar